Guide to the PricewaterhouseCoopers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Coopers & Lybrand Series IX: Books and Monographs
  - Subseries IX.2: Books on Accounting
    - Pomeranz, Felix; Ramsey, Gordon P.; Steinberg, Richard M. Pensions: An Accounting and Management Guide, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1976 (Box 50)
      [Inscribed by Pomeranz to Firm's Librarians]
    - Steinberg, Richard M.; Dankner, Harold Pensions: An ERISA Accounting and Management Guide, Second Edition, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1983 (Box 50)
    - Steinberg, Richard M.; Dankner, Harold Pensions: A Financial Reporting and Compliance Guide, Third Edition, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1987 (Box 50)
    - Steinberg, Richard M.; Murray, Ronald J.; Dankner, Harold Pensions: A Financial Reporting and ERISA Compliance Guide, Fourth Edition, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1993 (Box 50)
      [Signed by Steinberg and Murray]
    - Hunt, Alfred The Management Consultant, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1977 (Box 50)
    - Burke, William J; Zaloom, Basil J. Blueprint for Professional Service Corporations, New York: Dan & Bradstreet, Inc., 1970 (Box 50)
    - Taylor, Philip; Nelson, Benjamin O. Management Accounting for Hospitals, Philadelphia: W. B. Saunders Co., 1964 (Box 50)
      [Inscribed by P. Taylor to Jim Mahon, Jul 1964]
    - Karol, Nathaniel H.; Ginsburg, Sigmund G. Managing the Higher Education Enterprise, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1980 (Box 50)
    - Anderson, Richard E.; Meyerson, Joel W. Financing Higher Education in a Global Economy, New York: Macmillan Publishing Co. & American Council on Education, 1990 (Box 50)
    - Jones, Seymour; Cohen M. Bruce. The Emerging Business: Managing for Growth, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1983 (Box 50)
    - Sevin, Charles H. Marketing Productivity Analysis, New York: McGrew Hill Book Company, 1965 (Box 50)
    - Stasey, Robert; McNair, Carol J. Corssroads: A JIT Success Story, Homewood, IL: Dow Jones-Irwin, 1990 (Box 50)
    - Sasieni, Maurice; Yaspan, Arthur; Friedman, Lawrence Operations Research: Methods and Problems, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1959 (Box 50)
  - Subseries IX.3: C&L History Books
    - Ross, Edward T. Pioneers of Organized Public Accountancy in Pennsylvania, Philadelpha: Edward Stern & Co., Jan. 1942, 2 copies ( (Box 51)
    - Cooper Bros. A History of Cooper Brothers & Co: 1854 to 1954, London, 1954 (Box 51)
    - Leach, Campbell W. Coopers & Lybrand in Canada, 1976 (Box 51)
    - Flower, Raymond C&L Singapore Lords of the Abacus: 100 Years of Coopers & Lybrand in Singapore 1890 - 1990, Singapore, 1991 (Box 51)
    - C&L Building Values and Traditions: 100 Years of Coopers & Lybrand, New York, 1998 (Box 51)
  - Subseries IX.4: Monographs: Solutions for Business Series
    - C&L Singapore Asia and Australia Tax Summaries, 1994, Singapore, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Lamble, Peter; Low, Robin C&L International The Asia Pacific Insurance Handbook, [Sydney, Australia], 1995 (Box 51)
    - C&L International International Insurance Industry Guide, Fifth edition, 1993 (Box 51)
    - C&L USA Financing Source Guide, 1992 (Box 51)
    - C&L USA REITs: The Future is Now, 1992 (Box 51)
      [REIT - Real Estate Invesment Trust]
    - C&L Tax Primer: Corporate Investment into the People's Republic of China, 1994 (Box 51)
    - C&L Netherland Tijd als kritische factor, 1993 (Box 51)
      [In dutch]
  - Subseries IX.5: Other Monographs
    - Nobles, Christopher C&L Accounting Comparisons UK/Europe, Vol. 2 (Second Edition): Belgium, Italy and Spain, London, 1992 (Box 51)
    - Kabialis, Edward W.; Benzon, John W. C&L Accounting for Income Taxes: Evaluating the Proposed Rules, 1986 (Box 51)
    - Testoni, Louis l.; Favia, Frank V.; Hoagland, Calvin R.; Street, Janet A. C&L USA Accounting for Income Taxes: Focusing in on FASB Statement 96, 1988 (Box 51)
    - C&L USA An Analysis: 1984 Tax Legislation, Washington, DC, 1984 (Box 51)
    - C&L USA Choosing a Business Entity in the 1990's, Washington, DC, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Lenrow, Gerald I.; Marblestone, Philip K.; DiGilio, Anthony J. C&L USA Continuing Developments in the Taxation of Insurance Companies: 1995 - The Year in Review, Washington, DC, 1996, 2 copies ( (Box 51)
    - Smith, Jay M. Auditing Section of the American Accounting Association; C&L Curriculum Innovation: Excellence in Audit Education, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Wilkerson, David; Cooksey, Clifton C&L Customer Service Measurement, Washington, DC, Mar. 1994 (Box 51)
    - Ellis, Richard W.; McCarthy, Dennis J. C&L Financial Reporting and Tax Practices in Nonferrous Mining, Sixteenth Edition, [1992] (Box 51)
    - C&L Canada The Glossary, Third Edition, 1981 (Box 51)
    - Brooks, Donald E.; Herz, Robert H. C&L USA Guide to Financial Instruments, Third edition, 1994 (Box 51)
    - C&L USA Independence, Contingent Fees, Conflicts of Interest, 1995 (Box 51)
    - Chuo C&L Consulting Japanese Investment in US Real Estate, Tokyo, Japan, n.d. (Box 51)
      [In Japanese and English]
    - Financial Executives Research Foundation Retiree Health Benefits: Field Test of FASB Proposal, Morristown, NJ, 1989, 2 copies ( (Box 51)
    - C&L Stock Options: Accounting, Valuation, and Management Issues, New York, NY, 1993 (Box 51)
- Price Waterhouse Series I: Cataloged Documents
  - Subseries I.1: Account Books
    Journals and ledgers with handwritten bookkeeping records.
    - Price Waterhouse Private Journal No. 1, Canada, 1914-1921, 505p (14 x 9.5 x 2) (Box 52, Folder 1)
      [fragile]
    - Private Journal No. 2, Canada, 1922-1924, 500p (14 x 9.5 x 2) (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Ledger, 1937, 300p (14 x 8 x 2) (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Ledger, 1937, 300p (14 x 8 x 2) (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Ledger, 1938, 300p (14 x 8 x 2) (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Ledger, 1938, 300p (14 x 8 x 2) (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Private Ledger, n.d., 2 (10 x 8.5 x 1.5) (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
      [Locked]
    - Ledger No. 7, 1944-1945, 300p (13 x 8.5 x 1.5) (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Ledger No. 8, 1945-1946, 300p (13 x 8.5 x 1.5) (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Calendar-Notebook, private, 1897 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Subseries I.2: George O. May Awards and Certificates
    - Instutute of Chartered Accountants in England and Wales Examination Certificate: Passed Intermediate Examination, placed in order of Merit, Exeter, UK, Jan. 22, 1895, 1 (13 x 8) (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Instutute of Chartered Accountants in England and Wales Certificate: May, clerk to T. Andrew addmitted as Associate Not In Practice, Exeter, UK, Feb. 3, 1897, 1 (15 x 12) (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Instutute of Chartered Accountants in England and Wales Examination Certificate: Passed Intermediate Examination, placed in order of Merit, Exeter, UK, Feb. 9, 1897, 1 (13 x 8) (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Instutute of Chartered Accountants in England and Wales Certificate of Merit: May passes the Final Examination, awarded the First Prize, UK, Feb. 25, 1897, 1 (17 x 14) (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Instutute of Chartered Accountants in England and Wales Certificate of Membership, UK, Aug. 4, 1915; Nov. 3, 1920, 2 (15 x 10.5) (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Instutute of Chartered Accountants of Ontario Certificate authorizing May to use the apellation Chartered Accountant, Toronto, Canada, Oct. 28, 1910, 1 (16 x 15) (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - Instutute of Chartered Accountants of Ontario Certificate admitting May as a Fellow of Instutute, Toronto, Canada, Jan. 29, 1937, 18 x 14) (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - Instutute of Chartered Accountants of Ontario Articles of Clerkship: May to serve as clerk for Thomas Andrew, Chartered Accountant, Exeter, UK, Feb. 6, 1892, 1 (20 x 15) (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - American Association of Public Accountants Annual Certificate of Membership, New York, Oct. 2, 1902, 1 (15.5 x 13) (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - University of Illinois Certificate: May passed examinations for Expert Public Accountant and is registered by University as Certified Public Accountant (CPA), IL, Dec. 5, 1903, 1 (17 x 15) (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Executive Department Certificate: May passed examinations and is granted to practice as Certified Public Accountant (CPA), Harrisburg, PA, Jan. 25, 1913, 1 (20 x 16) (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - Permanent Blind Relief War Fund Certificate that May is a contrubutng member, Mar. 31, 1921, 1 (8 x 11) (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - Vittorio Emanuele III King of Italy Certificate: May recieves dell'Ordine della Corona d'Italia (Order of Italian Crown), Italy, Aug. 15, 1921, 1 (14 x 10) (Box 349, Folder 6)
      [original and copy]
    - State Board of Certified Public Accountants of Louisiana Certificate: May passed examinations and is registered by Board as Certified Public Accountant (CPA), LA, Apr. 2, 1931, 1 (17 x 14) (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - New York State Society of Certified Public Accountants Certificate: May elected a member of Society, NY, Oct. 1, 1931, 1 (17 x 14) (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - Academy of Political Science Certificate: May enrolled as a Life Member of Academy, New York, NY, Dec. 16, 1936, 1 (8 x 11) (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art Certificate: May is a Fellow in Perpetuity, New York, NY, Jan. 21, 1952, 1 (14 x 10.5) (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - American Institute of Accountants Award for book Financial Accounting, n.d., 1 (15 x 11) (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - War Trade Board Chairman's letter and $1.00 check for one year's service with the Board, Washington, DC, Jul. 17, 1919, 1 (t. l. s.), 1 (Treasurer of US check) (Box 349, Folder 7)
      [Mounted and framed]
    - [Carter] Glass Secretaru pf the Treasury Letter thanking for long patriotic service, Washington, DC, Oct. 8, 1919, 1 (t. l. s.) (Box 349, Folder 8)
  - Subseries I.3: Certificates-various employees
    - Brundage, Persival F. Beta Alpha Psi Certificate of initiation to fraternity, 21-May-49, 1 (8 x 10) (Box 349, Folder 9)
    - Gardner, Gordon F. State of Michigan Board of Accountancy Certificate entitling to practice as CPA, Detroit, MI, Feb. 4, 1952, 1 (12 x 11) (Box 349, Folder 9)
    - Mills, Leslie University of Illinois Certificate: Mills passed examinationsand is registered by University as Certified Public Accountant (CPA), Sep. 19, 1951, 1 (8.5 x 11) (Box 349, Folder 9)
    - Lothrop, Ernest Orville American Institute of Accountants Certificate of Membership, Jul. 11, 1922, 1 (15 x 12) (Box 349, Folder 9)
    - Lothrop, Ernest Orville New York State Society of Certified Public Accountants Certificate of Membership, NY, Jan. 15, 1932, 1 (17 x 14) (Box 349, Folder 9)
    - Thurston, Royal Church, Jr. State of Michigan Board of Accountancy Certificate entitling to practice as CPA, Detroit, MI, Apr. 8, 1948, 1 (12 x 11) (Box 349, Folder 9)
  - Subseries I.4: George O. May Files
    In 1897, George O. May, hired by the Price Waterhouse London Office several months earlier, begins his work in New York. By 1911 London office selects George O. May to succeed retiring senior partner Arthur Dickinson. During the First World War May served as a member of the Secretary of the Treasury's staff in 1917-18. Concurrently, he offered a subscription in Price Waterhouse name for the $25,000 to establish AIA library. G. O. May served on the AIA Committee on Federal legislation (first example of cooperation between the government and the profession to promulgate accounting principles), together with Robert H. Montgomery. In 1926 May assumed the role of economist-accountant-philosopher for the profession, and William B. Campbell succeeded him as a senior partner. G. O. May often represented accounting to the world and helped to shape the regulatory reforms of the 1930s and to promote generally accepted accounting principles.
    - Sub-subseries I.4.1: Arranged Correspondence
      Original arrangement from the PW record center retained: alphabetical by subject then chronologically. Mostly bound in blue books by Price Waterhouse information center, with some loose materials added. Database, partially cataloging the correspondence, can be found in Centennial Research series ( box 82, folders 13-15, box 83 folder 1) in hard copy. The digital copy of the same file is stored in as ascii text file on 3.5 floppy disk (box 96, Digital Materials). Originally, the database was created using Inmagic Db/Textworks software. All folders include letters, papers and memoranda by G. O. May. Other correspondents' names in this series were taken from the corresponding records of the Inmagic database.
      - Brundage, P. F.; Baldwin, Roger S.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA General. 1928-1930 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Kohler, E. L.; Richardson, A. P.; Smith, Archie M.; Carey, John L.; Whitney, Harvey E.; Waterhouse, Nicholas; American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1933-1936 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Dawson, John P.; Carey, John L.; Collins, Clem W.; Hasmer, W. A.; Sanders, T. H. American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1938-1939 (5) (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Carey, John L.; Collins, Clem W.; Bailey, George D.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1939 (6-11) (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Hosmer, W. A.; Sanders, T. H.; Carey, John L.; McNeill, H. M.; Carter, A. H.; Teele, Arthur W. American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1939 (12-19)-1940 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Gale, Frank A.; Sanders, T. H.; Farrand, George N.; Schuyler, William M.; Johnstone, H. M. American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Blough, Carman G.; Carey, John L.; Hazlitt, Henry; Paul, Randolph; Sanders, T. H.; Finch, J. K. American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1943-1944 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Caffyn, Harold R.; Noyes, Charles E. American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1947-1948 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Blough, Carman G.; Carey, John L.; Johnstone, Helen M.; Stewart, Harold; American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1949 (1-5) (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Brundage, Percival F.; Carey, John L.; Papworth, William S. American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1949 (6-11) (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Carey, John L.; Webster, Norman E.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1951-1952 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Dohr, James L.; Inglis, John B.; Cannon, Arthur M.; Webster, Norman E.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1953-1956 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Seidman, J. S.; Deeming, William S.; Carey, John L.; Cannon, Arthur M.; Bevis, Herman W.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1957 (1-7) (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Bevis, Herman W. American Instutute of Accountants AIA General, 1957 (8-13) (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Bowman, A.; Paton, William A.; Andrews, Frederick B.; Claire, Richard S.; Mathieson, John K.; Carey, John L. American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1937- 1939 (1-8) (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Carey, John L.; Nissley, Warren W. American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1939 (9-17) (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Gailey, George W.; Andrews, F. B.; Sanders, T. H.; Werntz, William W.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1939 (18-24) (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Carey, John L.; Claire, Richard S.; Nissley, Warren W.; Paton, William A.; Andrews, F. B.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1939 (25-31) (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Bailey, George D.; Carey, John L.; Claire, Richard S.; Nissley, Warren W.; Collins, Clem W.; Sanders, T. H.; Fernald, H. B. American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1939 (32-41) (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Carey, John L.; Sanders, T. H.; Atkins, Harold B.; Horne, Henry A.; Kracke, Edward A.; Nissley, Warren W.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1939 (42-43)-1940 (1-5) (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Bailey, George D.; Brennan, Cecil N.; Brownell, George A.; Carey, John L.; Chamberlain, Henry T.; Couchman, Charles B.; Cranstoun, William D.; Dean, Arthur H.; Devine, Carl T.; Fernald, H. B.; Haskell, John.; Henderson, A. I.; Littleton, A. C.; MacFarland, George O.; May, George O.; McCrea, Roswell Co.; Nissley, Warren W.; Paton, William A.; Sanders, T. H. American Instutute of Accountants; Lawyer's Club.; AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1940 (6-7) (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Sanders, T. H.; Horne, Henry A.; Werntz, William W.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1940 (8-15) (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Brundage, Percival F.; Kerrigan, Harry D.; Sanders, T. H.; Mathieson, John K.; Couchman, Charles B.; Seidman, J. S.; Farrand, George N.; Paton, William A.; Werntz, William W.; American Instutute of Accountants; US Treasury Department AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1940 (16-20)-1941 (1-2) (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Sanders, T. H.; Farrand, George N.; Herrick, Anson; Buchan, Leslie J.; Seidman, J. S.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1941(3-9) (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Carey, John L.; Farrand, George N.; Atkins, Harold B.; Farrand, G. N.; Fernald, H. B.; Dohr, James L.; Seidman, J. S.; Bailey, George D.; Montgomery, Robert H.; Werntz, William W.; Sanders, Thomas H. American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1941(10-16) (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Fernald, H. B.; Horne, Henry A.; Jones, J. Weldon.; Jones, Ralph C.; Staub, Walter A.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1941(17-25) (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Farrand, George N.; Carey, John L.; Sanders, T. H.; Paton, William A.; Dohr, James L.; Herrick, Anson; Kracke, Edward A.; Staub, Walter A.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP) (Inventories, LIFO Method), 1941(26-31)-1943 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Carey, John L.; Dohr, James L.; Farrand, George N.; Paton, W. A.; Dohr, James L.; Snow, Howard.; Horne, Henry A.; Broad, Samuel J.; Carey, John L.; Bailey, George; Brundage, Percival.; Kracke, Edward A.; Staub, Walter A.; Inglis, John American Instutute of Accountants; Securities and Exchange Commission; Ernst & Ernst. AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1944 (1-4) (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Bailey, George D.; Bell, William H.; Bowman, Archibald; Broad, Samuel J.; Dohr, James L.; Knight, Paul K.; Nissley, Warren W.; Peloubet, Maurice E.; Sanders, T. H.; Stans, Maurice H.; Carey, John L.; Staub, Walter A.; Werntz, William W.; American Instutute of Accountants; Securities and Exchange Commission AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1944 (5-12) (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Bell, William H.; Brundage. Percival; Dohr, James L.; Farrand, George N.; Herrick, Anson.; Horne, Henry A.; Nissley, Warren W.; Paton, William A.; Peloubet, Maurice E.; Knight, Paul K.; Smart, Jackson W.; Staub, Walter A.; American Instutute of Accountants; Leslie, Banks & Co. AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1944 (13-19) (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Farrand, George B.; Dohr, James L.; Cohen, Milton H.; Staub, Walter A.; Werntz, William W.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1944 (20-26) (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Blough, Carman G.; Nissley, Warren W.; Bailey, George D.; Carey, John L;; Dohr, James L.; Staub, Walter A.; Simpson, H. B.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1944 (27-35) (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Appel, C. J.; Bailey, George D.; Barber, Sidman I.; Blough, Carman G.; Boggs, Harry.; Bond, Joseph.; Dohr, James L.; Herrick, Anson.; Peloubet, Maurice E.; Schaffer, Walter L.; Scovill, H. T.; Staub, Walter A.; West, Philip L. American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1944 (37-43)-1945 (1-2) (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Blough, Carman G.; Graber, Paul J.; McLaren, N. Loyall; Nissley, Warren W.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1945 (6-11)-1947 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Bailey, George D.; Broad, Samuel J.; Knight, Paul K.; Paton, William A.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1948-1951 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Dohr, James L.; Grady, Paul.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1952-1954 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Blough, Carman G.; Herrick, Anson.; Eaton, Marquis G.; Jennings, Alvin R.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Accounting Procedure (AIA-CAP), 1956-1957 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Couchman, Charles B.; Leidesdorf, Samuel D.; Lybrand, William M.; Rukeyser, Merryle Stanley.; Bowman, Archibald.; Campbell, William B.; Carey, John L.; Carter, A. H.; Hoxsey, J.M.B.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Cooperation with Stock Exchanges, 1930-1931 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Couchman, Charles B.; Leidesdorf, Samuel D.; Lemaster, Eustace; Carey, John L.; Carter, Arthur H.; Hill, George W.; Moore, H. A.; Olson, Lyle H.; Staub, Walter A.; American Instutute of Accountants; New York Curb Exchange. AIA Committee on Cooperation with Stock Exchanges, 1932-1933 (1) (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Fernald, Henry B.; Chinlund, Edwin F.; Redmond, A. H.; Leidesdorf, S. D.; Bowman, Archibald; Carey, John L.; Carter, Arthur H.; Fedde, A. S.; Haskell, John G.; Hayes, James H.; Hill, George W.; Hoxsey, J.M.B.; Moore, Hoyt A.; Nissley, Warren W.; Olson, Lyle H.; Richardson, A. P.; Sanders, T. H.; Whitney, Harvey E.; American Instutute of Accountants; Seidman & Seidman. AIA Committee on Cooperation with Stock Exchanges, 1933 (2-3)-1940 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Aoyagi, Bunji; Bevis, Herman W.; Carey, John L.;; Grady, Paul; Hoxsey, J. M. B.; Jennings, Alvin R.; Nissley, Warren W.; American Instutute of Accountants; New York Stock Exchange; American Accounting Association AIA Committee on Cooperation with Stock Exchanges, 1941-1960 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Cooperation with Securities and Exchange Commission ( memorandum re: auditors' reports; accountants-duties and responsibilities.), 1935 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Carey, John American Instutute of Accountants; National Bureau Of Economic Research. AIA Committee on Federal Taxation: 1941 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Auld, George P.; Berger, R. O. American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Federal Organization, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Bevis, Herman W.; Seidman, J. S.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Long-Range Objectives, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Blough, Carman G.; Sanders, T. H.; Knight, Paul K. American Instutute of Accountants; Federal Power Commission AIA Committee on Public Utility Accounting (includes Montana Power Co. Case.), 1940-1945 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Grady, Paul.; Jennings, Alvin R. American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Relations with Securities and Exchange Commission, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Bailey, George D.; Mathieson, John L.; Carey, John L.; Sanders, T. H.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Terminology, 1939-1940 (1-6) (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Bailey, George D.; Carver, Charles.; Fedde, A. S.; Mathieson, John L.; Sanders, T. H.; Smith, Charles W.; Carey, John L.; Webster, Norman E.; American Instutute of Accountants AIA Committee on Terminology, 1940 (7-14) (Box 56, Folder 15)